<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C49FA6F7-DCA0-4B62-93CD-3DE058E493B2">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120522" date="2012-05-22 18:20:48 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Simply Elegant Sales Released!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Colorado Springs, Colorado -- February 3, 2006 -- Zarra Studios LLC (&lt;a href="http://www.zarrastudios.com/"&gt;www.zarrastudios.com&lt;/a&gt;) announced today the release of its flagship product, Simply Elegant Sales. Simply Elegant Sales is a premier small business point of sale (POS) application that was designed from the ground up exclusively for Apple's Macintosh OS X "Tiger." This unique POS system is designed with an efficient keyboard workflow for fast and accurate order processing. It can also track in store credit and utilize PayPal as your credit card clearing house.&#xD;Simply Elegant Sales can cache all of the credit card transactions and do a bulk submission at the end of the day or week. This permits the business owner to reduce costs that are generally associated with credit card processing, such as those at trade shows or conventions. The POS system also provides standard invoice processing, inventory tracking, purchase order management, and employee hour monitoring. Simply Elegant Sales also offers automatic discounts for sales as well as layaways, gift cards and store credit.&#xD;Explains Marcus Zarra, owner of Zarra Studios, "Our primary goal is to provide reasonably priced high quality business centric software for Apple's OS X operating system. Currently there are very few choices when it comes to Point of Sale software for OS X, and most of those have been ported from other operating systems or are priced at an extremely high point. Simply Elegant Sales is targeted at small retailers who should not be forced to pay more for their Point of Sale software than the hardware on which they are running it."&#xD;Simply Elegant Sales represents a completely native Cocoa solution designed exclusively for OS X, with a primary focus of delivering a fast and accurate check-out experience for the end customer. The workflow for invoice processing is streamlined to work completely via keyboard commands or by mouse menus. A cashier can choose the most efficient process, avoiding needless delays while searching through cascading menus to find the correct option for the customer's order.&#xD;Simply Elegant Sales has very modest hardware requirements. If your Macintosh is capable of running OS X 10.4 "Tiger" then it is more than sufficient to run Simply Elegant Sales smoothly.&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Pricing and Availability&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;Two versions of Simply Elegant Sales are available:&#xD;The entry edition ($129.00US) is designed for the business owner who may already have a credit card processing solution in place and does not wish to manage employee hours via Simply Elegant Sales.&#xD;The standard edition ($249.00US) is designed for the business owner who wishes to have credit card processing and employee hours tracked through one application. Teaming up with two very well known credit card clearing houses: First Data and PayPal, Simply Elegant Sales provides the business owner with a choice of vendors to handle their credit cards with more choices on the way in the very near future.&#xD;The software is available immediately. A demonstration copy is fully functional and is only limited by the number of invoices and purchase orders that can be created. You can download a copy today from our website: &lt;a href="http://www.zarrastudios.com/product_seSales.php"&gt;www.zarrastudios.com/product_seSales.php&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Background&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;Zarra Studios LLC was founded in 2005 with the goal of providing quality business software to the Macintosh community. Today, with the release of its flagship product, they are well on their way to filling the gaps in business software for OS X.&#xD;Press Contact:&#x2028;Marcus S. Zarra&#x2028;Zarra Studios LLC&#x2028;&lt;a href="mailto:mzarra@zarrastudios.com"&gt;mzarra@zarrastudios.com&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;NOTE TO EDITORS: For additional information visit Zarra Studios' website at &lt;a href="http://www.zarrastudios.com/"&gt;www.zarrastudios.com&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;Application screenshots are available at:&#x2028;&lt;a href="http://zarrastudios.com/ZDS/seSales_screenshots.html"&gt;www.zarrastudios.com&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;Zarra Studios is a trademark of Zarra Studios LLC.&#x2028;Other company and product names may be trademarks of their respective owners.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;i&gt;Friday, February 3, 2006&lt;/i&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
