<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C49FA6F7-DCA0-4B62-93CD-3DE058E493B2">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120522" date="2012-05-22 18:20:51 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;iWeb Buddy v1.1 Released&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Zarra Studios announced today the release version 1.1 to iWeb Buddy. iWeb Buddy is a post processor application for iWeb that is designed to bring additional functionality to iWeb that professionals and "pro-sumers" have come to need on their web sites. iWeb Buddy allows the user to add Google Analytics, Social Bookmarking and more to your website automatically. In addition, iWeb Buddy allows you to have multiple domain files in iWeb.&#xD;Colorado Springs, Colorado - Zarra Studios LLC announced today the release of iWeb Buddy v1.1. iWeb Buddy is a post processor application for iWeb that is designed to bring additional functionality to iWeb that professionals and "pro-sumers" have come to need on their web sites.&#xD;iWeb Buddy allows you to have multiple domain files with iWeb so that you can keep your sites separated into their own files. iWeb Buddy also post processes web pages created in iWeb; allowing the user to add Google Analytics, Social Bookmarking, Haloscan comments and custom HTML code to your website automatically.&#xD;In addition, iWeb Buddy remembers your settings, account numbers, etc. making it easy to update your website whenever you make a change in iWeb.  With iWeb Buddy, a user can "monetize" their websites that they have created in iWeb by being able to track the traffic on their sites, add custom html code for shopping carts and more.&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Additions / Enhancements&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;	&#x2022;	Automatically add Google Analytics to index.html files.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Automatically add Mint tracking to index.html files&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added the ability to update or add description metadata&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added the ability to update the title of pages (except blog entries)&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Updates / Corrections&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected some errors with Google Analytics file tracking.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected an error with the feed redirects not propagating to the archive page.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Fixed several hanging errors due to the screenshots.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Fixed itpc link redirects.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Fixed header redirect issue.&#xD;&lt;b&gt;About Zarra Studios, LLC.&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;Zarra Studios LLC was founded in 2005 by Marcus S. Zarra who has been developing software since the mid-1980s. &#xA0;Zarra Studios now serves the Macintosh community in both an educational capacity via the Cocoa Is My Girlfriend (&lt;a href="http://www.cimgf.com/"&gt;www.cimgf.com&lt;/a&gt;) blog and via its current software title, iWeb Buddy (&lt;a href="http://www.zarrastudios.com/ZDS/iWebBudy.html)"&gt;www.zarrastudios.com/ZDS/iWebBudy.html)&lt;/a&gt;. &#xA0;Zarra Studios is privately owned.&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;i&gt;Tuesday, October 14, 2008&lt;/i&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
