<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C49FA6F7-DCA0-4B62-93CD-3DE058E493B2">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120522" date="2012-05-22 18:20:49 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;seSales 1.4 Released!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>We are proud to announce that seSales 1.4 is released! &#xA0;This is a free upgrade to existing customers. &#xA0;This release completed the rental items release and is feature complete for the rental feature.&#xD;The following is a list of the major changes in this release:&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Enhancements&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;	&#x2022;	Inventory auto archive&#x2028;It is now possible to flag an inventory item for automatic archival. &#xA0;When the item runs out of stock, seSales will automatically flag it as archived.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Customer Notes&#x2028;Customer notes have been added to the customer management section of seSales. &#xA0;It is now possible to add as many notes to a customer record as needed and they are recorded by the date entered.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Default Invoice Note&#x2028;In a company's properties, a default invoice note can be set. &#xA0;Once set, it will display on every invoice that does not have a custom note defined.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Admin approval of instant discounts&#x2028;In a company's properties it is possible to set a flag that will require admin approval on all instant discounts when employee management has been activated.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Add Magnetic Card Reader Panel&#x2028;If you have a USB magnetic card reader, seSales can now utilize it for reading gift cards and credit cards.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Rental Rate Multiplier&#x2028;Rental rates can now be defined with multiple units such as $5.00 per 3 hours if desired.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Default Rental Rate&#x2028;For all rentals, a default can be set. &#xA0;This default will be used in the column display of the main window in item management.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Default Profit&#x2028;A default profit percentage can be set in the company's properties. &#xA0;Once set any new items added will use this setting to calculate either the retail price or the vendor price. &#xA0;This calculated price can still be overridden.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Purchase Units&#x2028;In the vendor management window, it is now possible to define bulk purchases from a vendor. &#xA0;For instance, when a box of candy bars are purchased as a single unit from the vendor but sold as multiple units, this can now be properly displayed and handled in the vendor management window.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Rental Renewal Invoices&#x2028;The handling of rental renewals has been altered. &#xA0;When a rental is renewed it now uses a new invoice instead of re-using the existing invoice.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Employee Hours&#x2028;In the employee management window, it is possible to edit the hours entered by an employee. &#xA0;&#xD;	&#x2022;	Customizable Payment Options&#x2028;In the properties window, it is now possible to add additional payment options in addition to the existing options.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Rental Rate Display&#x2028;The item management window can now display the rental rate as an optional column.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Restricted Items&#x2028;A new palette has been added to the item management window which allows the definition of item restrictions. &#xA0;These item restrictions can be a simple confirmation window or can require the cashier to input a value such as a birth date or driver's license number.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Address Book Syncing&#x2028;Address Book syncing is now disabled by default and can be re-enabled in the properties window.&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Reports&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;	&#x2022;	Labor Report&#x2028;The employee hours report has been revised. &#xA0;A start and end date can now be selected as well as the employee to report on.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Payments Report&#x2028;A new report has been added to show all payments received over a given time period. &#xA0;This report will include any authorization codes entered into the system and/or check numbers.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Report Export&#x2028;All reports can now have their primary data exported to a comma separated file for import into another application such as a spreadsheet or database.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Activity Reports&#x2028;The activity reports have been redesigned to reflect gross and net sales as well as taxes collected. &#xA0;These activity reports now accurately report refunds.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Instant Discounts Report&#x2028;A new report has been added to show all instant discounts given over a specific period of time. &#xA0;This report will also show the employee and admin who authorized the discount.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Inventory by Category Report&#x2028;The inventory report can now be generated only for specific categories.&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Issues&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;	&#x2022;	Returns On Credit Accounts&#x2028;When an item return is completed against an invoice that was charged to store credit, the refund will now accurately refund to store credit instead of cash.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Refund Processing&#x2028;Refund processing has had several corrections made to it. &#xA0;Items will now return to inventory if the flag is set in the company properties. &#xA0;The drawer will now accurately reflect any pay-outs for refunds.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Archived Items In Inventory Reports&#x2028;Archived items will no longer appear in inventory reports&#xD;	&#x2022;	New Item Creation&#x2028;An issue with new item creation while a search is active has been corrected. &#xA0;When a new item is created, the search field will be cleared.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Rental Agreement Duplication.&#x2028;This has been corrected. &#xA0;Rental agreements will only be printed once per invoice.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Bulk Price Change Freeze Corrected&#x2028;The bulk price change window will no longer freeze seSales while working with a large data set.&#xD;&lt;a href="perma://BLHome//"&gt;MSZ&lt;/a&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;i&gt;Monday, January 1, 2007&lt;/i&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
