<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C49FA6F7-DCA0-4B62-93CD-3DE058E493B2">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120522" date="2012-05-22 18:20:50 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;iWeb Buddy officially released!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Today, iWeb Buddy is available for purchase and download.  This is a very exciting time as you can now use iWeb Buddy to post process the pages created in iWeb and add the following features to your website:&#xD;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Multiple Domains&#x2028;&lt;/b&gt;Need to keep your websites separate but iWeb won&#x2019;t let you?  iWeb Buddy allows you to create as many domains as you want!  Simply open the domain you want to work on from within iWeb Buddy and it will automatically tell iWeb which domain to open for you!&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/b&gt;&#x2028;You can automatically add Google Analytics to every page in your site.  Use Google&#x2019;s web site tracking software to find out exactly who and when it coming to your site.  You can even use analytics to help promote your site and assist you in targeting the audience you are aiming at.&#xD;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Social Bookmarking&lt;/b&gt;&#x2028;With a simple configuration you can tag your blog entries with your favorite social bookmarking links and let your readers post your blog entries to them.  Places such as Digg, Slashdot, etc. are already included!&#xD;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;RSS Redirection&lt;/b&gt;&#x2028;Like to use Feedburner but iWeb doesn&#x2019;t work with it?  iWeb Buddy can change that for you automatically!  Feedburner will let you know who is reading your blog and how often they are looking for new content!&#xD;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;RSS Links in Blog Entries&lt;/b&gt;&#x2028;Wish iWeb would let your readers subscribe to your RSS feed from an entry?  iWeb Buddy fixes this for you automatically!  Whenever iWeb Buddy processes your website, it will automatically add the appropriate links to your blog entries to allow your reader to easily subscribe to your blog.&#xD;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;Custom HTML Code&lt;/b&gt;&#x2028;iWeb does a great job on some custom html but when you need the code directly on the page and not in an iFrame that is where iWeb Buddy comes to the rescue!&#xD;	&#x2022;	&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/1E32A74A-3F34-49D2-90DA-6A05F4D10CD1"&gt;And More....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;All of this for only $25.00!  You can download iWeb Buddy today and demo it, fully functional, for 30 days.  I am sure by the end of that time that you will agree that it is a must have utility for anyone who uses iWeb!&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;i&gt;Wednesday, March 5, 2008&lt;/i&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
