<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C49FA6F7-DCA0-4B62-93CD-3DE058E493B2">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120522" date="2012-05-22 18:20:48 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;seSales v1.4 Beta 1 Available&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Zarra Studios released Beta 1 of their upcoming version 1.4 release of seSales. &#xA0;&#xD;&lt;a href="http://zarrastudios.com/mint/pepper/tillkruess/downloads/tracker.php?uri=http://zarrastudios.com/files/seSales.zip"&gt;Download Now!&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;Several major enhancements are included in this release. &#xA0;However, this is a beta release and a few things should be noted:&#xD;This release is not &#x201C;feature complete&#x201D; but is &#x201C;data complete&#x201D;. &#xA0;What this means is that while some features are not completed yet, all of the required data and data entry is complete. &#xA0;Barring any unforeseen situations, there will not be another data migration for this release prior to the final release. &#xA0;As the beta progresses the additional features required and expected will be added. &#xA0;However we wanted to get this release out into your hands to confirm that all of the data that is needed is in place.&#xD;With that said, listed below are the current release notes. &#xA0;These notes will be updated with subsequent releases:&#xD;Completed Features:&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added the ability to handle rental items which includes the ability to print rental agreements directly on the invoice and track rental items by a unique identifier such as a serial number. &#xA0;Rental items can have multiple rental rates defined for them and will automatically select the appropriate rental rate.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added universal key bindings. &#xA0;Any menu item can now have a key binding assigned to it.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added a new customizable 80mm receipt printer format. &#xA0;Any paper size that is under 4" wide will automatically use the 80mm format.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added a MYOB compatible invoice/sales export.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added MYOB compatible inventory export.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added MYOB compatible customer export.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added check to ensure the company data file is writable.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added ability to flag a customer and/or invoice as tax exempt.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added ability for company administrators to edit the date of an invoice.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added additional data validation on Item Management.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added additional data validation on Vendor Management.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added additional data validation on Customer Management.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Increased the frequency of background saves to the company file while doing data entry in the Item, Vendor and Customer Management windows.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added ability for the Item Management window to detect when the productID pattern changes and update the pattern for future items added.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added defaulting of category and taxes to the settings used on the last item added to facilitate data input.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added productID to inventory export.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Updated the Print Copy and moved it to the File Menu to be more consistent with the Apple UI Guidelines.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added default to automatically close an invoice's window once the invoice has been posted.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Removed Invoice Posting confirmation. &#xA0;Canceling out of the print window will now cancel the posting of an invoice.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added the ability to force the creation of a drawer prior to creating an invoice.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added ability to open a different company file instead of migrating data in the current company file.&#xD;Localizations:&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added Canadian Localization.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Added Great Britain Localization.&#xD;Bug Fixes:&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected an issue in the audit creation that was preventing the ability create new inventory audits.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected an issue with the syncing of new customers with Address Book.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Altered the creation of new items in the item management window to default to a quantity of 1.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected an issue when canceling out of adding a credit payment to a customer&#x2019;s account.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected keyboard flow on PayPal payment entry sheet.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Removed the initial registration dialog window pop-up on Company loading.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected the display of payment dates on invoices.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected issue with display of archived discounts.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected display issues on the Discount Management window.&#xD;	&#x2022;	Corrected an issue with the calculations used in the print invoice. &#xA0;It is now possible to rearrange the columns: description, quantity and cost.&#xD;Note:&#xD;This release will perform a database migration on your company data file. &#xA0;The company data file will be copied to a backup prior to the migration. &#xA0;As with any data migration it is possible an error will occur. &#xA0;Please back up your company file before proceeding with the data migration.&#xD;If you choose to download and work with this beta please send all comments, bugs, issues &lt;a href="mailto:support@zarrastudios.com"&gt;support@zarrastudios.com&lt;/a&gt;. &#xA0;As always, your support and review of this beta will ensure that all of the issues are identified and corrected prior to the final release.&#xD;&lt;a href="perma://BLHome//"&gt;MSZ&lt;/a&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;i&gt;Tuesday, July 4, 2006&lt;/i&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
